const QUESTIONS = [
    {question:"How many seasons has good mythical morning been on youtube?",
    rightAns:15, ans2:7, ans3:20, ans4:10},
    {question:"What word causes Rhett to yell into the camera for an extended amount of time?",
    rightAns:"Tokyo",ans2:"mythical",ans3:"danger",ans4:"banana"},
    {question:"What is the name of Rhett and Link's podcast?",
    rightAns:"ear biscuits",ans2:"good mythical podcast",
    ans3:"hairpod",ans4:"now hear this"},
    {question:"What fishy food does Link absolutely despise?",
    rightAns:"sushi",ans2:"sardines",ans3:"tuna",ans4:"clams"},
    {question:"What year did good mythical morning first air?",
    rightAns:2012,ans2:2008,ans3:2005,ans4:2010},
    {question:"What hot pepper did Rhett and Link eat in one of their most viewed videos?",
    rightAns:"carolina reaper",ans2:"scorpion",ans3:"habenero",
    ans4:"ghost"},
    {question:"What is the name of the series of videos nicknamed the show after the show?",
    rightAns:"good mythical more",ans2:"good mythical extra",ans3:"good mythical two",ans4:"another mythical morning"},
    {question:"Who is taller, Rhett or Link?",
    rightAns:"Rhett",ans2:"Link",ans3:"they are the same height",ans4:"dont pick this one"},
    {question:"What gross food is often featured on the popular 'will it' segments?",
    rightAns:"pigs blood",ans2:"sheep brains",ans3:"cow eyeball",
    ans4:"toenails"},
    {question:"What was the name of the first show Rhett and Link created before good mythical morning?",
    rightAns:"good morning chia lincoln",ans2:"the mythical hour",
    ans3:"one mystical morning",ans4:"good morning with Rhett and Link"}
  ]
  
  